Characters (Cont.)

DR. EGGMAN (aka Dr. Ivo Robotnik)
With an IQ of 300 and a love of machines, Eggman dreams of world
conquest in order to create his own robotic utopia “Eggmanland”.
He sees the Time Stones as the perfect tool for world conquest
and will stop at nothing to get them.










METAL SONIC
The ultimate robot doppelganger, Metal Sonic was built by
Eggman to rival Sonic’s power and speed in every way.
Programmed to follow Eggman's agenda, he’s out to cause trouble
for not only Sonic, but poor Amy too!