Essential Items

Collect rings to stay in the game.
If Sonic has at least one ring he won't lose a
life when he gets hit. Collect 100 rings to gain an additional life.




Monitors contain various power-ups for Sonic:
Super Ring, Shield, Power Sneakers, Invincibility and 1-Up.




A Lamp Post records your present score and time the moment
you touch it. If you lose a life in that Zone, you will start
your next Life at the last Lamp Post you touched.