Special Moves

ROLLING SPIN ATTACK
• Tap Down on the DPad while moving to perform a rolling spin attack

SPIN DASH (Genesis Mode)
• While standing still, touch and hold Down, then tap the Jump Button
to rev up like a turbo engine. 
• Keep tapping to increase the power of the Spin Dash
before releasing the D-Pad.

SPIN DASH (Original Mode)
• While standing still, touch and hold Down, then tap the Jump Button
  to rev up like a turbo engine.
• Maximum speed will be achieved when the Spin Dash is given
  time to charge before releasing the D-Pad.

SUPER PEEL OUT
• While standing still, touch and hold Up, then tap the Jump Button.
  Sonic’s feet will start racing at turbo speed.
• Release the D-Pad to blast off in a blaze of blue!
• Sonic is vulnerable to attack during a Super Peel Out.