Special Stage

If you reach the Goal while carrying 50 rings or more, a
large golden Ring will appear at the end of the level. Jump
into it to enter the Special Stage.
The Special Stage is a 3D obstacle course scattered with
UFOs. If you can destroy all of the UFOs before the timer
runs out, you’ll pick up a Time Stone. Collect all seven
before Dr. Eggman finds them!

Each UFO conceals one of the following items:
• Power Sneakers give you an extra burst of speed
• Super Ring increases your ring count
• Time Bonus  adds 30 seconds to the timer

Some of the other items in the Special Stage will help you.
Others will make the course even more difficult! Watch out
for the water, it will shave 10 seconds off your timer.