The Time Warp


Time Warp signs, marked Past and Future are scattered around
each Zone. When you hit one of these signs a Past or Future
symbol appears next to the Lives display. You can now perform
a Time Warp!

When you start moving fast enough, you’ll see bright stars trailing
behind Sonic. If you can keep up your speed for a few seconds, the
Time Warp will blaze into effect.

Sudden changes in speed, slowing down or coming within range of
the Goal will cancel the Time Warp. You can try again as long you
have a Past or Future symbol in your possession.