The Time Warp (Cont.)





You can use the Time Warp signs to travel between the
Past, Present and Future.  Since the Future isn’t yet written,
there are two different possibilities: a future where Little Planet
is free from Dr. Eggman’s control, or a future where Eggman has
wreaked havoc!

To ensure a good future for a Zone, you must either collect all the
Time Stones, or destroy Eggman’s robot transporter contained
within the Past.