Characters

SONIC THE HEDGEHOG
With a spirit like the wind, Sonic is the world's fastest hedgehog
who lives for adventure. Despite his carefree attitude, he has a
strong sense of justice and is always ready to help those in need.










AMY ROSE
A bright and energetic girl who likes fortune telling and
mystic things. Amy is drawn to Little Planet after a tarot card
reading which tells of a destined encounter with Sonic.