A World That Defies Time



Little Planet; a tiny world filled with beauty and mystery.
Appearing over Never Lake for just one month a year, it is a place
where the past, present and future collide, thanks to the
mysterious Time Stones that lie hidden deep within the planet.

Hoping to catch a glimpse of this cosmic event, Sonic travels to
Never Lake, followed by star-struck Amy Rose,only to find the
once-beautiful world chained and imprisoned beneath a twisted
metallic shell. The evil genius Dr. Eggman has come for the
Time Stones, and with them may soon be able to command
time itself!

Can Sonic stop Eggman and free Little Planet?